("Tainted Love" by Soft Cell)
♪ Sometimes I feel I've got to run away ♪
♪ I've got to get away ♪
♪ From the pain you drive
into the heart of me ♪
♪ The love we share seems to go nowhere ♪
♪ And I've lost my life ♪
♪ For I toss and turn I
can't sleep at night ♪
♪ Once I ran to you I ran ♪
♪ Now I run from you ♪
♪ This tainted love you've given ♪
♪ I give you all a boy could give you ♪
♪ Take my tears and
that's not nearly all ♪
♪ Tainted love ♪
♪ Now I know I've got to run away ♪
♪ I've got to get away ♪
♪ You don't really want any more from me ♪
♪ To make things right you need
someone to hold you tight ♪
♪ And you think love is to pray ♪
♪ But I'm sorry I don't pray that way ♪
♪ Once I ran to you I ran ♪
♪ Now I run from you ♪
♪ This tainted love you've given ♪
♪ I give you all a boy could give you ♪
♪ Take my tears and
that's not nearly all ♪
♪ Tainted love ♪
♪ Don't touch me please I
cannot stand the way you tease ♪
♪ I love you though you hurt me so ♪
♪ Now I'm gonna pack my things and go ♪
♪ Tainted love oh ♪
♪ Touch me baby tainted love ♪
♪ Tainted love ♪